DJSOURMILK
HLIETOEEZD
HLIETOEE ZR
#LIFTOFF 7P-I2MID
JUSTINCREDIBLE
HLIETOEEZP-L2MID
#LIFTOFF 7P-I2MID
FAK
FA
一定的
Yeah,rest assured
最牛逼的活灵活现的在这里呢
The best is here in'-the flesh and that's for sure
剩下的应该穿个防弹衣我为了战争准备好按下录像键
The rest should wear'emra-vest;l'm set for war, nigga, press record
我派人去跟上帝说话
Isend niggas to address the Lord
和给你脖子上放把刀一样的flow
Same flow that put your neck to sword
让你马子脱衣服一样的flow
The same flow.that just undressed your whore
完全接管看看现在的分数
Takeover,-nigga, check the score
这是国际象棋最好看看棋盘上什么状况
This is chess, better check your board
谁给了这世界更多的炸货但是得到的奖励却少的可怜
Who gave the World'more fire but got less reward?
没啥压力我猜可能少即是多吧
No stress;myonly guess is,that less is more, more orless
我衣柜抽屉里面放个几十万我有福
Hundred Gsin my dresser drawer,I'm blessed
希望国税局别因为这事儿查我我还新手呢
Hope RS don't arrest me for it, I'm new to it
我新房子你能看到时报广场的景
My newcrib got'the Time Square view to it
与此同时两个妹子躺我床上习惯了
while twobitches'tay in my bed,I'mu used to it
你的闺蜜在给我嗦嘞现在该你了
That's your bestfriend -givin'me head, now you do it
你瞅也没那么奇怪
See mami-it's not so weird
我完事之后把你砍掉就好像毕加索的耳朵
After I hit,I cut you off like Picasso ear
记错了梵高还是谁天哪cole 你可太聪明了
Van Gogh or whoever,goddamn Cole, you're too clever
好像一个james Brown的采样
Like a fucking James Brown sample, you're two ever
乘以2那是永远高音推高点
Times two;that's forever, more treble
意思是给你这个级别上点更高端的招数
Meanin'-more highrend shit on your level
把对上帝的敬畏塞给他们我是纯粹的恶魔
Put the fear of God.in-niggas, I'm pure Devil
走着对立的路线就是对我的描述
walkin'contradiction, my description
即兴魔术师创作非虚构
Off the top magicianCompositions non-fiction
在竞争中胡作非为
Shitted in.the competitions
就好像尿壶一样消失吧拜拜
Pot to piss in,gone, uh, so long, uh
周六我以前一般修草坪
Saturdaysa.nigga-used'to mow lawns, uh
现在老子吃大虾
Nowadays anigga be eatin' prawns
贴着窗户干跟那些往里看得人打招呼
Fuckmy bitch bythewindowywave to the peeping Toms,uh
我是卡罗莱纳最牛逼的
Yes,I'm.Carolina's finest
盖着纽约邮戳的南部兄弟
Southern nigga with-New York stamps, honest
和Fiends在皇后区我是你的陛下
Out in Queens with'the fiends, I'm your highness
Cote world别人错了
Cole World,don't mistake it for a sinus
传染都这时候了我就显摆显摆
Infection,rat-this point, I'm just flexin'
Bas是下一个上场的时间就是检测
Bas is nextin line, and the test is time
把事儿做对了她妈就能退休了
Play the game,right-nigga, hegon' rest his mom
在苏丹的沙子上享受好好歇着了
In the sandsof sudanwhere she rest her mind
天伦之乐因为她的孩子会走起来
And find:peace'cause her son'll be fine
他背后有座城市支持他而我有他支持
He got the cityon his back, and I got him on mine
你觉得我在说谎吗？第一步让Fayetteville进入说唱版图
You think I'm lyin?shit,step one, got the 'ville on map
我估摸着在我的说唱里我已经做到了
shitl predictedin-my raps, Idone did allthat
接下来活吞了那些rapper恩结账
Next please,eatrappers, mm, check please
他们拿着我的账单的时候给他们小费(整句双关抓着我ball的时候给他们喷射)
Here's a tip whileniggas grip my testes
你想要开火？那就开火别招我
You wan'shoot?-Then'shoot, don't play with me
自奴隶制之后南部最狠的
Hardest shit out.the South since slavery, nigga
Hardest shit out.the-South'since slavery, nigga
VVU
VOLUN
今天早上起来就在想应该帅气逼人还是低调点"
Uh, woke up this morning and wondered'Hey, should I get fresh or should I keep it humble?"
我的衣柜好像是DoverStreetMarket(商店品牌名)过去还是个无业游民呢
My closet like Dover-Street, used to be bummin'
现在我还是会上街游手好闲区别就是我现在是自愿的
Some days I'm still-bummin',the difference is now it's by choice
穿好了衣服看眼外面这些人都不一样了
Got dressed and peeped out'the window, these lil' niggas different
他们不玩任末堂了他们玩加长弹仓了
They don't play.Nintendo, they play with extendos
我希望你们能活下来
iope-you can limbo
那些机枪会把你打的转圈好像是好声音上面的导师
Thatchopperg gonspin-you-around like a judge on The Voice
我来的地方大部分人都不够有福
I'm from a city where most niggas never get lucky enough
能够看到那个小地方之外的东西
To see somethin outside county limits
我把数字搞大了我没别的事儿
I ran up the digits, I don't have no muh'fuckin' business
没啥可抱怨的
Complainin'about nothin'
对他们搞得什名单没时间也没耐心
Ain't got no time or no'patience for lists they be makin'
或者是那帮聊谁更牛逼的
Or who.they debatin'is better
让我们承认吧他是最牛逼的之一
Let's face it,he one ofthe greatest
不是Bill Cosby那样的但如果有人敢小看我那就点他们
No Bill Cosby shit,butif niggas is sleepin', then fuck'em
大部分人不理解我
Most niggas·don't understand me
我不上格莱美我会穿着我的睡衣躺沙发上
I don't do the GRAMMYs,I'be in my jammies on sofa
大部分人不理解我
Most niggas-don't understand me
不管是法拉利还是凯美瑞我坐什么车里都是帅的
Ferrari orcalnrytbetrtook good in'em both
大部分人甚至都不明白
Most:niggas don't even get this
cole你怎么都最顶了还不玩妹子
Cole, How you ontopbut-you don't gotno bitches?I know
大部分人甚至都不明白
Mostniggas don't even get this
所以一旦有了机会他们用家人换了有钱人
So given the chance, they trade family forriches,I know
看看我的天花板没头
Look at.my ceilin', it's endless
我受够了这帮自怨自艾的了
I'm sick and these bitch niggas feelin'the sickness
他们身体里没那么多维C
Itain'tenoughvitamin cin they system
来摆脱我我会大杀特杀
To get rid of me-l'ma kill it relentless
地位在顶了 但是我听上去好像还是在壕沟(比喻贫民区)里面一样
On top, but I'sound like I'm still in the trenches
我来自Fayetteville我把反派变成受害者
I come from that'Ville,Iturn villains to victims
过来瞅瞅提到你的时候都是"R.I.P."
Reach andsee"R:l:p"fill up your mentions
这是给那些感觉自己要干点什么的人信息
Amessagetor-niggas'that's feelin' ambitious
"他怎么还没到过巅峰?"
"How come a niggastill ain't hit his prime?"
Off-Season5月14日发
Ahh,you-bitch,off-season comin' May 14th
你们所有你们完蛋了
Fuck allyall higgas, it's over for you
保证
swear to God
AVIOM
YOUTUBE.COM/POWER106